Hallelujah!
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
There is one strange thing that keeps disturbing us on the social media concerncing
the Thailand football team with thirteen players who are trapped in a cave.
Please, raise up your voice. They are little children.
It disturbs the whole world. It has become worldwide.
Please, open your lips. Ask God to intervene and rescue these children.
Because every minute, the news about them is so frightening -
that they cannot carry them because there is too much water.
These children are crying; they are lamenting.
They cannot spend more than...
Please, open your lips and pray for God's intervention.
The divers and the people that want to rescue them -
God should inspire them what to do and how to do it.
There is nothing on this earth... With God, all things are possible.
Yes, the Lord should rescue these children -
rescue them, help them, in Jesus Christ's name!
Amen!
RV: Mel Flowers 16/07/2018